I DON'T THINK IT'S A LITTLE
BIT.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A LITTLE BIT
LIKE, LAUGH AT THEM.
I WISH I HAD A HOODIE ON.
ARE WE TRYING TO PLAY SORORITY
SISTER AS ELECTED OFFICIAL?
I WAS AT A SORORITY OVER THE
WEEKEND IN TEXAS.
I FEEL LIKE I WAS BACK AT THE
SORORITY HOUSE.
THEY HAD MORE SENSE.
WE KNEW HER BRAIN DIDN'T WORK.
NOW WE KNOW THEIR EYES DON'T
WORK.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A LITTLE
BIT.
I THINK YOU SHOULD JUST GET A
HOODIE.
YOU SHOULD JUST WEAR A HOODIE
FROM NOW ON AND RESPOND TO HER
IN A HOODIE.
SHE SHOULD BE HOODIE TO HOODIE.
GO AHEAD.
I THINK THE IMPORTANT POINT
IS THAT EVERY TIME SHE'S ON TV,
REPUBLICAN APPROVAL RATINGS GO
UP, DEMOCRAT APPROVAL RATINGS GO
DOWN.
THAT LADY IS A WALKING NIGHTMARE.
AND YOU'RE ABOUT, I KNOW YOU
FOR 20 YEARS, YOU'RE ABOUT 5'10
YEARS AGO.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HEY, SEAN HANNITY HERE.
HEY, CLICK HERE TO SUBSCRIBE TO
FOX NEWS YOUTUBE PAGE AND CATCH
OUR HOTTEST INTERVIEWS AND MOST
COMPELLING ANALYSIS.
YOU WILL NOT GET IT ANYWHERE ELSE.